[{"question": "Identify wrong C Keywords below.", "option1": "A) auto, double, int, struct", "option2": "B) break, else, long, switch", "option3": "C) case, enum, register, typedef", "option4": "D) char, extern, intern, return", "ans": "D"}, {"question": "Identify wrong C Keywords below.", "option1": "A) union, const, var, float", "option2": "B) short, unsigned, continue, for", "option3": "C) signed, void, default, goto", "option4": "D) sizeof, volatile, do, if", "ans": "A"}, {"question": "Identify wrong C Keywords below.", "option1": "A) static, while, break, goto", "option2": "B) struct, construct, signed, unsigned", "option3": "C) short, long, if, else", "option4": "D) return, enum, struct, do", "ans": "B"}, {"question": "Find a correct C Keyword below.", "option1": "A) breaker", "option2": "B) go to", "option3": "C) shorter", "option4": "D) default", "ans": "D"}, {"question": "Find a correct C Keyword below.", "option1": "A) work", "option2": "B) case", "option3": "C) constant", "option4": "D) permanent", "ans": "B"}, {"question": "Find a correct C Keyword.", "option1": "A) Float", "option2": "B) Int", "option3": "C) Long", "option4": "D) double", "ans": "D"}, {"question": "Types of Integers are.?", "option1": "A) short", "option2": "B) int", "option3": "C) long", "option4": "D) All the above", "ans": "D"}, {"question": "Types of Real numbers in C are.?", "option1": "A) float", "option2": "B) double", "option3": "C) long double", "option4": "D) All the above", "ans": "D"}, {"question": "signed and unsigned representation is available for.?", "option1": "A) short, int, long, char", "option2": "B) float, double, long double", "option3": "C) A & B", "option4": "D) None of the above", "ans": "C"}, {"question": " Size of a Turbo C C++ compiler is.?", "option1": "A) 16 bit", "option2": "B) 32 bit", "option3": "C) 64 bit", "option4": "D) 128 bit", "ans": "A"}, {"question": " Size of a GCC or Visual Studio C Compiler is.?", "option1": "A) 16 bit", "option2": "B) 32 bit", "option3": "C) 64 bit", "option4": "D) 128 bit", "ans": "B"}, {"question": " Sizes of short, int and long in a Turbo C C++ compiler in bytes are.?", "option1": "A) 2, 2, 4", "option2": "B) 2, 4, 4", "option3": "C) 4, 8, 16", "option4": "D) 8, 8, 16", "ans": "A"}, {"question": " Sizes of short, int and long in Visual Studio or GCC compiler in bytes are.?", "option1": "A) 2, 2, 4", "option2": "B) 2, 4, 4", "option3": "C) 4, 4, 8", "option4": "D) 4, 8, 8", "ans": "B"}, {"question": " Range of signed char and unsigned char are.?", "option1": "A) -128 to +127\n0 to 255", "option2": "B) 0 to 255\n-128 to +127", "option3": "C) -128 to -1\n0 to +127", "option4": "D) 0 to +127\n-128 to -1", "ans": "A"}, {"question": " Ranges of signed int and unsigned int are.?", "option1": "A) 0 to 65535\n-32768 to +32767", "option2": "B) -32768 to +32767\n0 to 65535", "option3": "C) -32767\u00a0to +32768\n0 to 65536", "option4": "D) 0 to 65536\n-32767\u00a0to +32768", "ans": "B"}, {"question": " Size of float, double and long double in Bytes are.?", "option1": "A) 4, 8, 16", "option2": "B) 4, 8, 10", "option3": "C) 2, 4, 6", "option4": "D) 4, 6, 8", "ans": "B"}, {"question": " Range of singed long and unsigned long variables are.?", "option1": "A) -2147483647\u00a0to +2147483648\n0 to 4294967295", "option2": "B) -2147483648\u00a0to +2147483647\n0 to 4294967296", "option3": "C) -2147483648\u00a0to +2147483647\n0 to 4294967295", "option4": "D) 0 to 4294967295\n-2147483648\u00a0to +2147483647", "ans": "C"}, {"question": " Range of float variable is.?", "option1": "A) -3.2e38 to +3.2e38", "option2": "B) -3.8e32 to +3.8e32", "option3": "C) -3.4e34 to +3.4e34", "option4": "D) -3.4e38 to +3.4e38", "ans": "D"}, {"question": " Left most bit 0 in Singed representation indicates.?", "option1": "A) A Positive number", "option2": "B) A Negative Number", "option3": "C) An Unsigned number", "option4": "D) None of the above", "ans": "A"}, {"question": " If you do not specify a storage class for a Variable.?", "option1": "A) You get compiler error.", "option2": "B) You get a compiler warning.", "option3": "C) Output is null always", "option4": "D) None of the above", "ans": "D"}]
